https://parts.pinnaclenissan.com/policy.aspx

Skip to Content
Shop OEM Nissan parts and accessories from our nationwide network of authorized dealers.
×
You can edit the name of your vehicle by clicking the pencil icon on the right.
+ Add New Vehicle
Something went wrong. Please try again.
Add Vehicle To Garage
×
Select Your Vehicle Below:
< Back
VIN
Go
No vehicles found. Please try again.
Select your vehicle below:
View Cart
It’s the season of giving, so we’re giving you one more reason to shop Nissan Parts & Accessories Online.
Shop now through 1/1/21 and get 15% off select parts and accessories from our online catalog.Online only. Restrictions apply. See terms and conditions for details.
SHOW MORE +
Home
Policies, Terms and Conditions
Jump To:
Policies
Shipping Rates
Tax Rates
Payment Types
Service Provider Policy
Refunds
Returns
Privacy PolicyTerms of UseWelcome to Nissan North America. Protecting your privacy is important to us here at Nissan North America.The purpose of the following statement is to help you understand how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information you provide on our web site.1. Information Collection: When you browse our web site, you do so anonymously. Personal information, including your E-mail address, is not collected. Your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) is logged to give us an idea of which pages of our web site you are visiting and how much time you spend there. We do not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable. The only other information automatically provided to us is the type of computer and operating system you are using. This information is supplied to us by your browser. There are forms on our web site requesting that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your E-mail address and possibly your postal address, for purposes such as correspondence, survey information, or requesting a quotation. Like many other commercial web sites on the Internet, ours may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how the site is used.2. Information Use: If you provide us with your E-mail address, or have done so in the past, we may occasionally send you E-mail offers. We may use information you have given us to, for example, provide a service, measure consumer interest in our various products, and inform you about new products and services. These offers may be based on information you provided in your initial transaction with us, in surveys, or from information that may indicate purchasing preferences and lifestyle.3. Declining E-mail Offers: We provide customers with an easy means to decline receiving E-mail offers. Although most customers tell us they appreciate receiving notice of these carefully designed opportunities, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers from us by simply replying to the E-mail and informing us of your preferences. All E-mail offers that you receive will inform you of how to decline receiving further E-mail offers.4. Children: Nissan North America does not market to children, nor do we solicit data from them. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, our web site by guests under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian.5. Company Commitment to Privacy: Nissan North America will never sell your information to others.6. Your Acceptance of These Terms: By using this site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.Sales are final.WarrantyAll Genuine NISSAN parts are custom-fitted, custom-designed, and durability-tested for your NISSAN, and come with a NISSAN-backed 12 month/12,000 mile (whichever occurs first) limited warranty (if installed by dealer at the time of purchase).Genuine NISSAN Accessories are covered by NISSANs Limited Warranty on Genuine NISSAN Replacement parts and Genuine NISSAN Accessories for the longer of 12 months/12,000 miles (whichever occurs first) or the remaining period under the 3-year/36,000-mile (whichever occurs first) NISSAN New Vehicle Limited Warranty. Terms and conditions apply. See Warranty Information Booklet for details.Website DisclaimerThis website is intended for general descriptive and informational purposes only. It is subject to change and does not constitute an offer, representation or warranty (express or implied) by Nissan North America, Inc. Interested parties should confirm the accuracy of any information in this website with their NISSAN retailer before relying on it to make a purchase decision. Nissan North America, Inc. reserves the right to make changes, at any time, without prior notice, in prices, colors, materials, fabrics, equipment, and specifications, and to discontinue parts or accessories. Due to continuous product development and other pre- and post-production factors, actual parts, materials and specifications may vary from this website. Availability and delivery times may vary.
For additional information, see your NISSAN retailer or contact Nissan North America, Inc.Promotion DetailsValid online through 12/31/20 at 11:59 p.m. CT at participating US NISSAN retailers only. Qualifying amount applies to Genuine NISSAN Accessories only. Does not apply to applicable taxes, installation or shipping and handling charges. Not valid on NISSAN replacement parts, Genuine Branded Merchandise, ICON Lift Kits, Yakima Accessories, or Japan Domestic Market (JDM) parts, accessories, merchandise and Motorsports parts. May not be combined with any other offers. Use coupon codes at online checkout. Discount will be reflected in shopping cart at online checkout. Coupon has no cash value. Other restrictions may apply.Shipping PolicyAll orders must have a valid Home or Business address. We do not ship to P.O. Boxes. Oversize items and Heavy Weight items, including but not limited to bumper components, body panels, engines, transmissions, require extra shipping charges; please email us for a quote before ordering. Please be specific as to what you want to have shipped and have the complete address to which it will be shipped. These items are necessary to give an accurate quote for shipping costs. If the actual shipping charges are more than what was calculated at checkout, you will be charged the additional shipping charges.Discontinued Parts: Not all discontinued and/or older parts and/or accessories are available for immediate shipment. Please call or email to confirm availability on shipping of discontinued and/or older parts and/or accessories. There will be no returns or exchanges on discontinued and/or older parts and/or accessories. They are considered “Final Sale.”
Core Policy: Some parts offered on our site have a "core charge" applied to them. This is a refundable charge that the manufacturer applies to ensure that the old part is returned to us. Customers are responsible for all shipping charges related to returning cores to us. Remember all core returns must be assembled, clean, complete with no missing parts, undamaged, and in the original packaging. If you have any questions about core charges please feel free to contact us and we will be happy to answer them.Return PolicyNo refunds after 30 days. All return parts must be in the original packaging and you must include a copy of your invoice. If your order did NOT include the VIN, there will be no returns or exchanges on the parts ordered! There are no returns on airbags, electrical, fuel, high performance parts, racing parts, previously installed, or special ordered parts, because we cannot restock them. There will be a 20% restocking fee for all returns if we concluded the order was your error, but still a returnable item. If the error is ours, we will cover shipping expenses and re-send the item to you. If the order error is the customers, charges for shipping and handling are not refundable.Please contact us for a Return Authorization Number, prior to returning any merchandise. If you choose to email us, please include your order number and "Return Authorization" in the subject line. Returns will not be accepted without a Return Authorization Number. Parts must be returned for inspection prior to any credit being issued. All return parts must be uninstalled and returned in the original, unopened, undamaged packaging or you will not receive credit. Parts must be accompanied by a copy of proof of purchase invoice (this can be found under “Your Account” on our site). All shipments must be prepaid. COD and freight collect shipments will be refused. If these requirements are NOT met, parts will be either scrapped or returned to you at your expense. Core Policy: Some parts offered on our site have a "core charge" applied to them. This is a refundable charge that the manufacturer applies to ensure that the old part is returned to us. Customers are responsible for all shipping charges related to returning cores to us. Remember all core returns must be assembled, clean, complete with no missing parts, undamaged, and in the original packaging. If you have any questions about core charges please feel free to contact us and we will be happy to answer them. Refund PolicyReturned products must be in new, unused condition and include the original box and/or packaging. Once we receive your return and inspect it (usually within 48 hours of receipt), your refund will be processed and a credit will be applied to your credit card or original payment methods. Please note that depending on your credit card company, it may take an additional 2-10 business days after your credit is applied for it to be posted to your account.
All returns need an RMA number obtained when you apply for a refund, and will need to be returned to our address which can be found on the About Us page of this website. You are responsible for all return shipping costs.
Shipping Rates
State/ProvinceCountryOrder TotalShipping Cost
USA$0.00 - $20.008.95
USA$20.01 - $50.009.95
USA$50.01 - $75.0010.95
USA$75.01 - $100.0013.95
USA$100.01 - $150.0016.95
USA$150.01 - $200.0022.50
Service Provider Data Privacy Policy
This business uses SimplePart, LLC as a Service Provider to build and maintain our parts website. For a privacy policy regarding the use of consumer data, please refer to our main website’s privacy policies page.
Payments Accepted
Close VIN entry layer
Enter VIN
Enter 17 digit VIN here
Go
ContactNISSANUSA.comNissan ServiceView NISMO CatalogNISMO Japan Parts and AccessoriesJDM NISMO MerchandiseAbout UsAccepted PaymentsContact UsPoliciesRefundsReturns
Legal
Terms of Conditions of Sale
Privacy PolicyWarrantyData Requests
Links
Dealer Home
My Profile
Wholesale Login
Testimonials
Find us on Pinterest
While every reasonable effort is made to ensure the accuracy of this data, we are not responsible for any errors or omissions contained on these pages. Please verify any information in question with a sales representative.
By continuing to use this website, you agree to our use of cookies to give you the best shopping experience. Terms of Conditions of Sale
© 2020
Nissan North America, Inc.
SPWEB37
